Finding Aid of the American Academy of Allergy, Asthma & Immunology Records, 1923-2015
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1923-2015, UWM Manuscript Collection 139; 257.9 cubic ft. (741 boxes) 40 binders 1 oversize folder 30,895 digital files (79.5 GB) 1 film reel 4 safety film negatives
  - 2. Annual Meetings, 1944-2011
    - Industry and Organization Guidelines for Participation, 2000 (Box 540, Folder 10)
    - Industry Participation Guidebook, 2002-2003 (Box 444, Folder 9)
    - Interest Section Symposia Syllabus
      - 1995 (Box 524, Folder 2)
      - 1996 (Box 524, Folder 1)
      - 1998 (Box 514, Folder 8)
      - 1999 (Box 514, Folder 6)
      - 2000 (Box 513, Folder 8)
      - 2001 (Box 444, Folder 10)
    - International Conference Brochure, 1996 (Box 465, Folder 22)
    - International Travel Grant Award, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Ladies Program, 1953, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Learning Center
      - Financial, 1989, 1991 (Box 455, Folder 4)
      - Reference Guide, 1985-1991 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Reference Guide, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Media Coverage
      - 1999 (Box 517, Folder 24-26)
      - 2000 (Box 504, Folder 5-6)
      - 2000 (Box 505, Folder 1)
      - 2001-2003 (Box 709, Folder 2-4)
      - 2009 (Box 712)
    - Meeting Planner
      - 2003/2004 (Box 368, Folder 17)
      - 2005 (Box 535, Folder 84)
      - 2006/2007 (Box 674, Folder 5)
      - 2008 (Box 708, Folder 4)
    - Message from President Bill Clinton, 1998 (Box 543, Folder 44)
    - News Clippings, 1950-1956 (Box 375, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters Published by Pharmaceutical Companies, 1969-1971, 1974-1976, 1990, 1993 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Odyssey Program, 2008 (Box 708, Folder 6)
    - Operations Manual
      - 1990 (Box 524, Folder 17)
      - 1991 (Box 524, Folder 7)
      - 1992 (Box 524, Folder 5)
      - 1993 (Box 524, Folder 19)
      - 1994 (Box 524, Folder 20)
      - 1995 (Box 524, Folder 21)
      - 1996 (Box 444, Folder 11)
      - 1997 (Box 514, Folder 4)
      - 1998 (Box 514, Folder 5)
      - 1999 (Box 524, Folder 18)
      - 2000 (Box 524, Folder 6)
      - 2001 (Box 513, Folder 3)
      - 2002 (Box 524, Folder 10)
      - 2003 (Box 524, Folder 4)
      - 2004 (Box 513, Folder 7)
      - 2005 (Box 537, Folder 90)
      - 2007 (Box 677, Folder 4)
      - 2008 (Box 708, Folder 7)
      - 2009 (Box 720, Folder 7)
      - 2010 (Box 720, Folder 11)
    - Participant List
      - 1948, 1951, 1955-1959, 1961-1990 (Box 36, Folder 1-7)
      - 1991, 1994-1995 (Box 321, Folder 9)
    - Participation Guidebook, 2001 (Box 321, Folder 10)
    - Physician Registrant Profile, 1992 (Box 321, Folder 11)
    - Planning and Logistics, 1999 (Box 709, Folder 5)
    - Pocket Guide/Pocket Program, 1989-1993, 1995, 1999-2001 (Box 321, Folder 12)
    - Positions Available in Allergy/Immunology
      - 2000 (Box 321, Folder 13)
      - 2003 (Box 491, Folder 4)
    - Positions Sought in Allergy/Immunology
      - 2000 (Box 321, Folder 14)
      - 2001 (Box 520, Folder 16)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 492, Folder 9-10)
    - Post Meeting
      - Asthma 99: Theory to Treatment, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Bahamas Post Convention Tour, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Hawaiian Session, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Las Vegas Post Meeting Symposium, 1991 (Box 375, Folder 12)
      - Post Meeting Symposium, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Poster Presentations [Reproductions], 1995 (Box 503, Folder 13)
    - Pre-Meeting, Pre-Convention Scientific Assembly, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - President's Grant-In-Aid Award, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Press Conference Schedule, 1997 (Box 463, Folder 2)
    - Press Kit
      - 1999 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - 2000 (Box 375, Folder 13)
      - 2001 (Box 444, Folder 14)
      - 2002 (Box 520, Folder 22)
      - 2008 (Box 708, Folder 4)
      - 2009 (Electronic \Series 02\, Electronic Annual Meeting Press Kit 2009\)
    - Press Releases, 1956-1958 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Press Releases and News Clippings, 1997-1998 (Box 458, Folder 3-4)
    - Proceedings
      - 1946 (Box 720, Folder 3)
      - 1949 (Box 720, Folder 4)
    - Program, Advance Registration, 1990-1991 (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - Program, Final
      - 1944-1948 (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
      - 1950-1951 through 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 4-14)
      - 1972-1973 through 1980-1981 (Box 479, Folder 1-5)
      - 1982-1983 through 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1-5)
      - 1991-1995 (Box 480, Folder 1-5)
      - 1996 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - 1997 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - 1998 (Box 322, Folder 4)
      - 1999 through 2002 (Box 481, Folder 1-4)
      - 2003 (Box 491, Folder 3)
      - 2004 (Box 526, Folder 17)
      - 2005 (Box 540, Folder 57)
      - 2006 (Box 674, Folder 6)
      - 2007 (Box 677, Folder 5)
      - 2008 (Box 708, Folder 8)
      - 2009 (Box 720, Folder 8)
      - 2010 (Box 720, Folder 11)
    - Program, Preliminary
      - 1965, 1967, 1971, 1975 (Box 444, Folder 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - 1992-1994 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - 1995-1997 (Box 321, Folder 15)
      - 1998 (Box 322, Folder 1)
      - 1999 (Box 512, Folder 6)
      - 2000 (Box 322, Folder 3)
      - 2001 (Box 428, Folder 16)
      - 2002 (Box 463, Folder 1)
      - 2003 (Box 493, Folder 5)
      - 2004 (Box 524, Folder 16)
      - 2005 (Box 534, Folder 3)
      - 2006 (Box 674, Folder 7)
      - 2007 (Box 674, Folder 9)
      - 2008 (Box 708, Folder 9)
      - 2009 (Box 720, Folder 9)
    - Puerto Rico Meeting, Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 322, Folder 5)
    - Reception, 2009 (Box 720, Folder 10)
    - Reception and Dinner Invitations, 2002, 2004 (Box 471, Folder 3)
    - Registration Forms, 1996-1998, 2000-2005 (Box 322, Folder 7)
    - Registration Packet
      - 1989-1990 (Box 375, Folder 14)
      - 1991 (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - 2000 (Box 375, Folder 15)
    - Resource Center, 2000 (Box 322, Folder 8)
    - Scientific Writers' Press Conference Schedule, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Self-Report Form for Continuing Education, 2001-2003 (Box 490, Folder 9)
    - Slide Presentation, 1993 (Box 322, Folder 6)
    - Social Events
      - 1950 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 35, Folder 7-8)
      - 1968 (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - 1969 (Box 322, Folder 9)
      - 1972 (Box 540, Folder 2)
      - 1974 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 10-11)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 12-13)
      - 1990 (Box 322, Folder 10)
      - 1991-1994 (Box 35, Folder 14-17)
      - 1996 (Box 537, Folder 96)
      - 1997 (Box 375, Folder 16)
      - 1999 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - 2000 (Box 322, Folder 11)
      - 2001 (Box 543, Folder 28)
      - 2002 (Box 543, Folder 13)
      - 2003 (Box 465, Folder 8)
      - 2005 (Box 471, Folder 7)
    - Sponsorship Opportunities, 2001 (Box 444, Folder 15)
    - Strategic Training in Allergy Research (ST*AR) Program, 2008 (Box 708, Folder 10)
  - 2A. Annual Meeting Handouts, 1946-2012
    Subseries includes materials distributed as the scientific sessions of the annual meeting. Materials are arranged chronologically and thereafter alphabetically by session title or numerically by session number. Researchers should consult the annual meeting programs for listings of sessions.
    - 1946-1980 (Box 37)
    - 1981-1988 (Box 38)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 39)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 40)
    - 1992
      - Sessions 301-434 (Box 41)
      - Sessions 436-630 (Box 42)
      - Sessions 631-718 (Box 43)
      - Courses (Box 44)
    - 1993
      - Sessions 205-607 (Box 45)
      - Sessions 608-716 & Courses (Box 46)
      - Postgraduate Education Course and Asthma Consultant's Course Syllabus (Box 47)
    - 1994
      - Sessions 501-615 (Box 48)
      - Sessions 616-772 (Box 49)
      - Sessions 773-871 (Box 50)
      - Sessions 872-915 & Postgraduate Courses (Box 51)
      - Postgraduate Plenary and Asthma Consultant's Course Syllabus (Box 52)
    - 1995
      - Sessions 656-1995 & Courses (Box 53)
      - Courses (Box 54)
      - Postgraduate Syllabus and Asthma Consultant's Course, 1995 (Box 493, Folder 8)
    - 1996
      - Sessions 1611-1682 & Courses (Box 54)
      - Sessions 1683-1830 (Box 55)
      - Sessions 1865-1955 (Box 56)
      - Sessions 1957-2027 & Courses (Box 60)
      - Postgraduate Syllabus (Box 465, Folder 23)
    - 1997
      - Sessions 2017-6502 & Courses (Box 60)
      - Postgraduate Syllabus (Box 514, Folder 9)
    - 1998
      - Courses (Box 60)
      - Postgraduate Syllabus (Box 514, Folder 7)
    - 1999
      - Sessions 1001-2513 (Box 323)
      - Sessions 2514-2834 (Box 714)
      - Sessions 2901-3532 (Box 466)
      - Sessions 3533-4401 (Box 467)
      - Sessions 4402-5020 (Box 468)
      - Sessions 5102-6007 (Box 509)
      - Sessions 6008-6503 & Courses (Box 510)
      - Postgraduate Syllabus (Box 513, Folder 10)
    - 2000
      - Sessions 3101-5526 (Box 525)
      - Sessions 5527-7519 (Box 535)
      - Sessions 7521-8501 (Box 536)
      - Postgraduate Syllabus (Box 513, Folder 9)
    - 2000-2004 (Electronic \Series 02A\, Electronic Annual Meeting Handouts and Posters\)
    - 2001
      - Sessions 1001-2720 (Box 536)
      - Sessions 2721-4701 (Box 687)
      - Sessions 4702-6203 (Box 688)
      - Postgraduate Syllabus (Box 444, Folder 12)
    - 2002
      - Sessions 1211-4813 (Box 688)
      - Postgraduate Syllabus (Box 471, Folder 6)
    - 2003
      - Sessions 1101-6035 (Box 462)
      - Sessions 4901-6103 (Box 711)
      - Postgraduate Syllabus (Box 491, Folder 1)
    - 2004
      - Postgraduate Syllabus (Box 526, Folder 19)
    - 2008
      - Abstracts (Electronic \Series 02A\, Electronic Annual Meeting Handouts and Posters\, Electronic 2008\)
        Use CD 49 access copy
      - Board Review Syllabi Books 1 & 2 (Box 741)
      - Handouts, 397 pdf files (Electronic \Series 02A\, Electronic Annual Meeting Handouts and Posters\, Electronic 2008\, Electronic Annual Meeting Handouts\)
        Use CD 47 access copy
      - Second International Gastrointestinal Eosinophil Research Symposium Handouts, 11 pdf files
        Use CD 50 access copy
    - 2009, 488 pdf files (Electronic \Series 02A\, Electronic Annual Meeting Handouts and Posters\, Electronic 2009\)
      Use CD 48 access copy
    - 2011
      - Session 4303 (Box 741)
    - 2012
      - Session 4101, Board Review Course Take Home Questions, Board Review Course Program Evaluation Forms, Board Review Course Syllabus Book 1, Board Review Course Syllabus Book 2 (Box 741)
  - 3. Newsletters and Publications, 1929-2015
    Included in this series are the Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology, AAAAI News, and a variety of short-term miscellaneous publications, newsletters, pamphlets, and reports.
    - 1942, Take a Step Back 50 Years Ago: Notes from the AAAAI Historian Burton Zweiman, M. D., [1992] (Box 493, Folder 6)
    - A/I Connection, 2000-2001 (Box 455, Folder 5)
    - Academy Insights, 1999 (Box 524, Folder 14)
    - AAAAI News, Published as News and Notes from 1948 to 1995, Academy News from 1995 to September 2006, and as AAAAI News beginning in October 2006.
      - 1948-1982 (Box 109, Folder 1-10)
      - 1983-1987 (Box 487, Folder 1-5)
      - 1988-1995 (Box 110, Folder 1-8)
      - 1995-1997 (Box 111)
      - 1998 (Box 484)
      - 1999 (Box 112)
      - 2000 (Box 485)
      - 2001 (Box 452)
      - 2002-2004 (Box 486)
      - 2005 (Box 538)
      - 2006
        - January-September (Box 712)
        - October-December (Box 713)
        - Annual Meeting ed. (Box 712)
      - 2007
        - January-December (Box 713)
        - Annual Meeting ed. (Box 712)
      - 2008
        - January-December (Box 713)
        - Annual Meeting ed. (Box 712)
      - 2009
        - Winter-Fall (Box 713)
      - 2010
        - Winter-Fall (Box 713)
      - 2011
        - Spring (Box 713)
        - Annual Meeting ed. (Box 713)
    - Adverse Reactions to Foods, 1984 (Box 326, Folder 15)
    - Adverse Reactions to Foods, a Patient's Guide, 1992, 1994-1995, undated (Box 326, Folder 16)
    - All About Allergies and Asthma, USA Today Supplement, 2000-2001 (Box 444, Folder 16)
    - Allergic Rhinitis Update for Family Physicians: Case Study Seminars, undated (Box 707, Folder 1-2)
    - Allergy and Asthma Report, in Discover
      - 1998 (Box 428, Folder 5)
      - 1999 (Box 380, Folder 4)
      - 2000 (Box 465, Folder 18)
      - 2001 (Box 517, Folder 32)
    - Allergy and the Immune System, Reprint from Scientific American, 1993 (Box 455, Folder 7)
    - Alliance Newsletter
      - 1989-1993 (Box 325, Folder 2)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - Anaphylaxis Retrospectives, 2006 (Box 707, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting News, 1996 (Box 524, Folder 26)
    - Asthma and Allergy Advocate
      - 1985-1990 (Box 326, Folder 2)
      - 1991-1995 (Box 459, Folder 5)
      - 1996-2001 (Box 459, Folder 6)
      - Index, 1995-1998 (Box 465, Folder 16)
    - Asthma and Allergy Management News, 1997 (Box 326, Folder 3)
    - Asthma Magazine's "Attending School with Managed Asthma and Allergies," 1999 (Box 520, Folder 24)
    - CAN! Connection, 2001-2002 (Box 520, Folder 45)
    - Chrysalis Project Newsletter, 1999-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 326, Folder 4)
    - Current Issues in Allergy and Immunology, 1990-1992 (Box 326, Folder 5)
    - Dedicated to Optimal Patient Care, 1998 (Box 503, Folder 9)
    - Defining Disease Management in Asthma and Allergy, 1997 (Box 326, Folder 17)
    - Disease Management Focus: Allergy, undated (Box 326, Folder 18)
    - Education and Research Trust Report, 1992, 1995 (Box 326, Folder 6)
    - Excerpts from Classics in Allergy
      - 1st ed., 1969 (Box 326, Folder 19)
      - 2nd ed., 1992 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Fellows in Training Newsletter, 1993-1995 (Box 326, Folder 7)
    - Firsts in Allergy, by Sheldon Cohen, 1983-1984 (Box 455, Folder 8)
    - From Cause to Cure,New York Times Magazine Supplement, 1999-2001 (Box 465, Folder 19)
    - Getting Up to Speed: The Allergy Practice and Managed Care, 1997 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - Healthnet, 1993 (Box 326, Folder 8)
    - Hotline, 1992-1995 (Box 326, Folder 9)
    - Impact, Vol. 20-21, 2014-2015 (Box 744)
    - The Importance of Allergic Disorders, 2000 (Box 428, Folder 7)
    - Improving Allergy and Asthma Care Through Outcome Management, 1997 (Box 327, Folder 3)
    - Insights in Allergy, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 17)
    - JCAAI Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 520, Folder 43)
    - Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology, Published as Journal of Allergy from November 1929 through June 1971 and thereafter as Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology
      - Vol. 1-3, 1929-1932 (Box 68, Folder 1-7)
      - Vol. 4-7, 1932-1936 (Box 69, Folder 1-7)
      - Vol. 8-10, 1936-1939 (Box 70, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 11-13, 1939-1942 (Box 71, Folder 1-4)
      - Vol. 14-17, 1942-1946 (Box 72, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 18-20, 1947-1950 (Box 73, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 21-23, 1950-1952 (Box 74, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 24-26, 1953-1955 (Box 75, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 27-29, 1956-1958 (Box 76, Folder 1-4)
      - Vol. 29-31, 1958-1960 (Box 77, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 32-34, 1961-1963 (Box 78, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 34-36, 1963-1965 (Box 79, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 37-39, 1966-1967 (Box 80, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 40-42, 1967-1968 (Box 81, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 43-45, 1969-1970 (Box 82, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 46-48, 1970-1971 (Box 83, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 49-51, 1972-1973 (Box 84, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 52-54, 1973-1974 (Box 85, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 55-57, 1975-1976 (Box 86, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 58-60, 1976-1977 (Box 87, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 61-63, 1978-1979 (Box 88, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 64-66, 1979-1980 (Box 89, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 67-69, 1981-1982 (Box 90, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 69-71, 1982-1983 (Box 91, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 72-73, 1983-1984 (Box 92, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 74-75, 1984-1985 (Box 93, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 76-77, 1985-1986 (Box 94, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 78, 1986 (Box 95, Folder 1-3)
      - Vol. 79-81, 1987-1988 (Box 96, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 81-83, 1988-1989 January-March (Box 97, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 83-88, 1989-1991 July, September (Box 98, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 88-90, 1991-1992 (Box 99, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 90-92, 1992-1993 (Box 100, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 93-94, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 94-96, 1994-1995 (Box 102, Folder 1-3)
      - Vol. 96-97, 1995-1996 (Box 103, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 98-99, 1996-1997 (Box 104, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 99-101, 1997-1998 (Box 105, Folder 1-6)
      - Vol. 101-102, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 3-6)
      - Vol. 103-104, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 1-5)
      - Vol. 105, 2000 January-June (Box 108, Folder 3-4)
      - Vol. 106, 2000 July-September (Box 505, Folder 2-8)
      - Vol. 107, 2001 (Box 537)
      - Vol. 109, 2002 January (Box 472, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 110, 2002 July-October (Box 715)
      - Vol. 111, 2003 February (Box 520, Folder 12)
      - Vol. 112, 2003 July-December (Box 702)
      - Vol. 112, 2003 September (Box 520, Folder 12)
      - Vol. 112, 2003 October (Box 520, Folder 1)
      - Vol. 112, 2003 November (Box 524, Folder 13)
      - Vol. 112, 2003 December (Box 524, Folder 3)
      - Vol. 113, 2004 February (Box 526, Folder 32)
      - Vol. 113, 2004 March (Box 526, Folder 22)
      - Vol. 114, 2004 November (Box 534, Folder 11)
      - Vol. 115, 2005 January (Box 534, Folder 12)
      - Vol. 115, 2005 February (Box 536, Folder 2)
      - Vol. 116, 2005 November (Box 707, Folder 4)
      - Vol. 117, 2006 January-June (Box 703)
      - Vol. 118, 2006 July-December (Box 704)
      - Vols. 119-120, 2007 (Box 716)
      - Vols. 121-122, 2008 (Box 717)
      - Vols. 123-124, 2009 (Box 718)
      - Vols. 125-126, 2010 (Box 724)
      - Vols. 127-128, 2011 (Box 725)
      - Vols. 129-130, 2012 (Box 726)
      - Vols. 131-132, 2013 (Box 727)
      - Vols. 133-134, 2014 (Box 742)
      - Vols. 135-136, 2015 (Box 743)
    - Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology: In Practice, Vol. 2-3, 2014-2015 (Box 744)
    - Legislative and Socio-Economic Issues in Focus, 1983-1988 (Box 326, Folder 10)
    - Managing Asthma Care, 1995? (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - Marketing Monitor, 1989-1995 (Box 326, Folder 11)
    - Medical Outcomes Trust Monitor, Asthma Outcomes, 1996 (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - Monograph on Insect Allergy
      - 1st ed., 1981 (Box 327, Folder 6)
      - 2nd ed., 1992 (Box 327, Folder 7)
      - 3rd ed., 1995 (Box 327, Folder 8)
    - National Resident Education Program News, 2001-2003 (Box 380, Folder 1)
    - Newsline, 1993-1994 (Box 326, Folder 12)
    - Notes From the Historian, 1940-1942 (Box 326, Folder 13)
    - Occupational Lung Disease-Asthma: A Bibliography, 1988 (Box 444, Folder 19)
    - Office Forms for the Allergist (Box 444, Folder 20-63)
    - Our Presidents [Academy History], 1993 (Box 327, Folder 9)
    - Pediatric Asthma: Research, Awareness Turn Tide on Disease, from Discover, April 2002 (Box 520, Folder 18)
    - Practice Issues, 1996-2000 (Box 326, Folder 14)
    - Practice Review Guide: Strategic Planning and Managed Care, 1997 (Box 327, Folder 10)
    - Primer on Allergic and Immunologic Diseases
      - Correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box 444, Folder 65)
      - 1st ed., 1982 (Box 327, Folder 11)
      - 2nd ed., 1987 (Box 327, Folder 12)
      - 3rd ed., 1992 (Box 444, Folder 64)
      - 4th ed., 1997 (Box 503, Folder 2)
      - 5th ed., 2003 (Box 524, Folder 30)
    - Respiratory Digest, 2001 (Box 543, Folder 15)
    - Rhinitis: Inflammation and Intervention, 2006 (Box 707, Folder 5)
    - Rinkel Method, JACI Reprints, 1980-1982 (Box 327, Folder 13)
    - Sinusitis: Bench to Bedside, Current Findings, Future Directions, Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology Supplement, 1997 (Box 444, Folder 66)
    - Spring Allergies and Asthma Survival Guide, from USA Today Advertising Supplement, 2002 (Box 465, Folder 14)
    - Task Force on Allergic Disorders: Promoting Best Practice, Meetings To Go Program, 2001-2002 (Box 707, Folder 6-7)
    - Time Supplement, 1988 (Box 455, Folder 9)
  - 4. Committees, Councils, and Interest Sections, 1944-2009
    This series contain minutes, correspondence, and related materials from the Academy's councils, interest sections, and various committees.
    - 25th Anniversary Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 254, Folder 10)
    - 2003 Annual Meeting Program Committee, 2002 (Box 494, Folder 5)
    - Abusive Practices, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1985 (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Acceptable Diagnostic Techniques, Subcommittee on, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Acceptable Practice Standards, Subcommittee on, 1987-1988 (Box 163, Folder 14-15)
    - Access to Care Subcommittee, 1993 (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - Adherence Committee, 2004 (Box 537, Folder 77)
    - Adverse Reactions to Biological Agents, 1992-1993 (Box 572, Folder 1)
    - Adverse Reactions to Drugs and Biologicals, 2000 (Box 543, Folder 39)
    - Adverse Reactions to Drugs Study Group, 1987 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Adverse Reactions to Foods Committee
      - 1984-1986 (Box 238, Folder 3-4)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 115, Folder 12-13)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 116, Folder 1-2)
      - 1991-1996 (Box 572, Folder 2-3)
    - Aerobiology Committee
      - 1994 (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - 1999-2001 (Box 678, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Committee
      - 1988-1990 (Box 137, Folder 6-9)
      - 1991-1993 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - AIDS, Advisory Committee on, 1988 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Air Processing Subcommittee, 1952-1965 (Box 163, Folder 16)
    - Allergen Standardization Committee
      - 1982-1983 (Box 238, Folder 6)
      - 1984-1987 (Box 116, Folder 5)
      - 1988-1994 (Box 116, Folder 6)
      - 1995-1999, 2001 (Box 543, Folder 18-19)
    - Allergic and Asthmatic Child in Schools Task Force, 1991 (Box 572, Folder 4)
    - Allergic Bronchopulmonary Aspergillosis Committee, Reports, 1993, 2004 (Box 445, Folder 1)
    - Allergic Reactions to Antibiotics Committee
      - 1989 (Box 116, Folder 7)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 667, Folder 1)
      - 1988 (Box 113, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 445, Folder 2)
    - Allergy and Immunology in Medical Schools
      - Ad Hoc Committee on, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 5)
      - Committee on, 1987-1992 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Allergy Care in the Indigent
      - Ad Hoc Committee on, 1985-1988 (Box 113, Folder 6)
      - Committee on, 1989-1992 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Allergy Foundation of America, Ad Hoc Committee to Work with the, 1969-1976 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Allergy to Animals
      - Committee on, 1979-1986 (Box 238, Folder 7)
      - Committee on, 1988-1989 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Allied Health Committee
      - 1988 (Box 116, Folder 8)
      - 1988-1995 (Box 316, Folder 1-7)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 116, Folder 10)
      - Office Assistants Program, 1989 (Box 455, Folder 10)
      - Reading List, 2000 (Box 428, Folder 6)
    - Allied Health Leadership Meeting, 2000 (Box 540, Folder 8)
    - Allied Health Membership Subcommittee, 2004 (Box 537, Folder 76)
    - Allied Health Professionals Committee, Agenda and Minutes, 1999 (Box 455, Folder 11)
    - Alternate Forms of Therapy, Committee on
      - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 122, Folder 8-9)
      - Mailings, 1963-1978 (Box 122, Folder 10-11)
      - Johns Hopkins Study of Rinkel Technique, 1980-1981 (Box 238, Folder 8-9)
    - Amalgamation Committee
      - 1955-1965 (Box 116, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box 445, Folder 3-4)
    - American Medical Association Section on Allergy, Ad Hoc Liaison Committee to, 1966-1971 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Anaphylaxis Committee, 1993, 1994, 1996, undated (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Animal Allergy Committee, 1971-1979 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Annual Meeting, Committee Minutes
      - San Francisco, CA, 1997 (Box 667, Folder 2)
      - Washington DC, 1998 (Box 667, Folder 3)
      - Orlando FL, 1999 (Box 667, Folder 4)